# Morgan Mastrangelo

## Software Engineer

- mmastrangelo1120@gmail.com
- **20/11/1994**
- **+**1 727 300 2593
- SAINT PETERSBURG, FLORIDA
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/morgan-mastrangelo-243ba0272
- nttps://github.com/morgan-mastrangelo



#### Profile

I'm a software engineer with 7+ years of project experience in all stages of web design and development. I'm also highly motivated to secure a job in an IT company where I can utilize my skills and knowledge in programming languages. I have a strong foundation in computer science principles and concepts of technology and experience in debugging applications using programming languages. I'm not only an experienced software engineer, but also a passionate full-stack engineer seeking to find the opportunity to work in a challenging environment that will encourage me to improve my necessary skills in order to be able to assist the company in achieving its mission, collaborating with team and project managers.

In addition, I have a rich experience as a UX/UI designer, specializing in creating intuitive and user-centered designs that look smart and improve the overall experience. One of my favorites is building a wonderful web design that cannot be found anywhere.



#### Skills

#### **Programming Languages**

C/C++, C#, Java, Python, Kotlin Go, Ruby, Rust, Perl, Swift, Matlab, Scala, HTML, CSS, SQL, XML, Javascript, Typescript, GraphQL

#### **Frontend Development**

ReactJS, Angular, AngularJS, VueJS, React Native, NextJS, NuxtJS

#### **Database Management**

MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Oracle, SQLite, MariaDB

#### **Content Management System**

WordPress, Shopify, Sanity

#### **Web Design**

Photoshop, UX/UI, Emotional intelligence, Motion

#### **Backend Development**

ExpressJS, Ruby on Rails, PHP, Laravel, Django, ASP.NET, Spring boot, Flask

#### **Version Control & Project** Management

GitHub, Gitlab, SVN, Visual Source Safe

#### Education

### **Professional Experience**

2016 - 2018	<ul> <li>Software Programmer, BCG</li> <li>Built several desktop applications with C/C++, QML, and mobile applications with Java.</li> <li>Designed a search feature for an open-source visual programming tool to help users better navigate the system.</li> </ul>	Miami, FL, United States
2018 - 2019	<ul> <li>Web Designer, CTI</li> <li>Designed Company Logo, Portfolio Blog, etc.</li> <li>Created high-quality and visually-appealing websites for small and medium-sized businesses according to their specific needs.</li> </ul>	Fort Lauderdale, FL, United States
2019 – 2020	<ul> <li>Frontend Web Developer, Uber</li> <li>Used Javascript, HTML, and CSS to develop web applications for various industries.</li> <li>Developed a booking application using React, Next.js, and Node.js to let users book a service online and get real-time updates on their progress.</li> <li>Followed a Kanban-style workflow using Trello boards.</li> <li>Created a mobile responsive web design for an online store that gets 65% of its traffic from mobiles.</li> <li>Worked with back-end developers, front-end developers, and full-stack developers to achieve client objectives.</li> </ul>	San Francisco, United States
2020 – 2022	<ul> <li>Senior Frontend Developer, ACG</li> <li>Taught 7 junior front-end developers and utilized their technical skills to achieve the organization's objectives.</li> <li>Developed a web interface using Vue to perform CRUD operations on tasks with large files, driving up the performance of a workflow pipeline by 60%.</li> <li>Designed a credit payment system with premium plans and integrated the application with Stripe API using Node.js to accept online payments.</li> <li>Converted given wireframes into Vue components and designed a mobile-friendly UI to provide a better user experience across multiple devices.</li> </ul>	Chicago, IL, United States
2023 – present	<ul> <li>Software Engineer, Pfizer</li> <li>Collaborated and managed teams in web application development, such as E-commerce, and social websites.</li> <li>Developed and maintained web applications using Django, AngularJS, and MySQL.</li> <li>Assisted with the deployment process using Docker and AWS services.</li> </ul>	New York, United States



### **Certificates**

**CSS Certificate on Hacker Rank** 

**SQL Certificate on Hacker Rank** Verified SQL Basic Programmer

Verified CSS Expert

C# Certificate on Hacker Rank ☑

Verified C# Programmer